blogtimenow.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is more important to us and so here at Blog Time Now we follow several set of rules to maintain your privacy.

#### **What information do we collect?**

We may collect personal identification information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources that we make available on our Site. You may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. You can however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities.

#### **Do we use cookies?**

**Yes** (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. You can turn off cookies anytime, but note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

#### **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, language preference, date and time of your request, the type of computer and technical information, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

#### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1.  To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2.  To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3.  To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

#### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### **Third party websites**

You may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licencors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

#### **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

#### **Changes to our privacy policy**

Blog Time Now has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us here](http://blogtimenow.com/contact/ "Contact Us").

This document was last updated on November 03, 2013
